很久很久以前 在一个遥远的银河星系....
这是一个无法无天的时代
各大犯罪集团互相争夺各种资源：食物 药品和超空间燃料
在造船业星球克雷利亚
邪恶的毗羲夫人强迫逃难者从事犯罪活动以换取她的庇护
在那脏乱的街头 一个为生计奔波的年轻人 渴望能翱翔于星辰大海
快点
Come on.
快点启动
Come on!
别让他跑了
Don't let him get away!
游侠索罗:星球大战外传
现在就进去
Get inside now!
快点 你迟到了
Hurry up! You're late!
看毗羲夫人不剥了你的皮
Proxima's gonna have your hide.
滚到洞里去
Get back in the den.
看我偷到什么了
Look what I stole!
毗羲会给我一份额外口粮的
Proxima'll give me an extra portion for this!
不 我觉得她会把额外口粮给我的
Nope, I think she's gonna give that extra portion to me.
还给我
Hey, give it back!
在谁手里就归谁
It belongs to whoever's holding it!
不是你的了
And that's not you!
莱克斯
Lex!
满点萨巴克
Full Sabacc!
笨蛋组合
Idiot's Array.
什么 给我看下
What? Let me see that!
不行 这是我的牌
Nope, it's my card.
你作弊
You cheat.
汉
Han!
你去了那么长时间
You were gone too long!
我就知道肯定是出事了
I knew something must've gone wrong.
我没事 倒霉的是他们
This is nothing. You should see them.
下来看看
Look down here!
听我说
All right, listen.
在交易的过程中
I was in the middle of the exchange,
我正准备交出核芯素
I'm handing over the coaxium
他的手下袭击了我 我耍了他们
and his goons jumped me, but I showed 'em.
你是怎么办到的
How?
我逃走了 然后偷了他们的飞车
I ran away, then I boosted their speeder.
我们是不是可以离开这里了
What, are we going somewhere?
没错 想去哪就去哪
Yeah, anywhere we want.
你偷了一管这个
You held on to one of the vials?
汉回来了 快去
Han's back!
这 这管东西值...
This, this is worth...
值五六百个信用点
Five, six hundred credits.
我们现在不缺钱了
That's more than you said we'd need.
那我们可以用这笔钱离开控制区了
To buy our way out of the control zone.
离开克雷利亚星球
And off Corellia.
汉 我们能远走高飞了...
Han, this could work.
肯定能远走高飞的
This is gonna work.
琦拉 你经常说 总有一天我们要离开这里
Qi'ra, you always said one day we're gonna get out of here.
这一天来了
This is it.
那我们还等什么
What are we waiting for?
他们在那 嘿 你们俩
There he is. Hey, you two!
莫克洛 你好吗
Moloch. Hi, how are ya?
我正准备去见毗羲夫人呢
I was just on my way to see Lady Proxima.
你还有钱还债吗
我这一晚上经历的事
What a night I had.
说出来你都不信 怎么说呢 我是...
You're not gonna believe it. You'll believe it, but...
搜他的身
不许动 臭老鼠
Hold still, scrumrat!
轻点儿
Easy.
快走
Come on.
好的
All right.
我们去见毗羲夫人
Let's go see Lady Proxima.
说说吧 怎么回事
Well, what happened?
我告诉您发生了什么
I'll tell you what happened.
他们背叛了您 还想杀了我
They double-crossed you and tried to kill me.
那钱呢
The money?
- 他们抢了 - 那我的核芯素呢
- They kept it. - And my coaxium?
他们也抢走了
They kept that, too.
不过倒是给我们上了一课
But we learned a very valuable lesson.
我们不能相信那群家伙
We cannot trust those guys.
所以你认为我们会相信你
So you expect me to believe
就看你这么两手空空的回来了
that you walked away with nothing!
我...带着小命逃回来的 不算两手空空吧
I ran away with my life. I think that's something.
我觉得我自己的命还是很重要的
To me, that's a lot.
我交给你这么简单的一个任务
I trusted you with a simple task,
你回来的时候却是满腹借口
and all I'm hearing are excuses.
不听话就得接受惩罚
There must be consequences for disobedience
不然你永远都不长记性
or else you never learn.
我告诉你
You know what?
我就是永远不长记性
I don't think I'm ever gonna learn.
你说什么
What did you say?
我说 以后谁再敢打我
I said, next time somebody hits me,
我就打回去
I hit 'em back.
莫洛克 等等
Moloch, wait!
不要
Don't!
琦拉 你还记得那个地窖吗
Qi'ra, remember the Silo?
我们把你解救出来
We pulled you out of that horror,
收留了你
gave you a home.
不要为了汉放弃这一切 他不值得你这样
Don't throw it away for Han. He's not worth it!
他在交易中损失的那些 我们会双倍赚回来
Whatever he lost on the deal, we'll earn it back, double.
我们会补偿您的
We will make it up to you.
所有人都给我退后
Everybody, stand back!
那是个什么玩意
What's that supposed to be?
这是一枚热能榴弹
This is a thermal detonator
我刚拉下了保险
that I just armed.
- 那是一个石头 - 不  不是
- That's a rock! - No, it's not.
就是石头
Yes, it is!
那咔嚓声
And you just made
是你用嘴发出来的
a clicking sound with your mouth.
别告诉我这就是你的计划
Please tell me this isn't your plan.
不 这才是...
No, this is.
- 上车 - 一辆M-68么
- Get in! - An M-68?
- 很不错吧 - 我喜欢
- Nice, right? - I love it!
我们坐从宝冠航空港
There's a starliner leaving from Coronet Spaceport,
起飞的星际航班
we're gonna be on it.
我们买通检查站的工作人员 然后就自由了
We bribe our way through the checkpoint, and we're free.
我要当飞行员
I'm gonna be a pilot.
我们可以买一艘属于自己的飞船
We can get our own ship.
我要飞遍整个银河系
See the galaxy, all of it.
以后我们再也不会受到任何人的摆布和欺负了
We won't have to take orders or be kicked around by anyone.
没错
Ever.
见鬼 他们这么快就追上来了
Thought we'd get a little more of a head start.
坐好
- Whoa! - Hang on!
这里属于管制区域
This is a secure area.
你必须持有访问许可
You must have proper clearance.
立刻停下 你必须遵守...
Stop at once! You must follow the proper...
规章制度
Protocol.
见鬼 那辆陆行艇好快
Damn! That stinger's fast.
是啊 我们更快 对吧
Yeah, but we're faster, right?
但愿如此
I hope so.
靠边停车
Pull over!
汉 我们过不去的
Han, no, we're not gonna make it!
是吗
Oh, yeah?
汉 不行 路太窄了
Han, I'm telling you, it's too tight!
看我的
Watch this.
放出猎犬
追上他们
快
Come on!
我们得走了
We gotta move.
没有登机牌的旅客
Do not join the line
不要排队
if you don't have a boarding pass.
没有身份证不得通过
No access without ID chip.
所有机器人必须登记
All droids must be registered.
快走 快走
Move along. Move along.
退后 不要抵抗
Stand down. Do not resist!
- 别挣扎了  - 你们放开我
- Stop struggling. - Let me go!
抓住他的手
Take his arm.
我抓住他了
I got him.
押到3B牢房
Take him to cell 3B.
这边 快走
This way, come on.
快走 抓紧了
Keep moving. Hold it, hold it.
下一位
Next.
汉 他们来了
Han, they're here.
你们干什么的...
Hey, what are you...
我们快到了
We're almost there.
- 你跟紧我 - 下一位
- Just hold on to me. - Next.
不要回头
Don't look back.
一旦通过了我们可得想好
Once we're through, we've gotta be smart,
接下来要去哪
figure out where we're going.
只要不是帝国的领域就行
Anywhere the Empire isn't. Wherever we go,
哪里都不会比这差
it can't be worse than where we've been.
这可说不好 在那边我们不受保护
Yes, it can. Out there, we've got no protection.
我们可能会被人贩子抓住
We could get snatched up by traffickers,
卖给血红黎明或者赫特人集团
sold to Crimson Dawn or the Hutt Cartel.
我绝对不会
That's not gonna happen.
让这种事情发生的
I won't let it.
护身符
For luck?
没错
Damn right.
知道了 我们走
You heard him. Let's go.
下一个
Next.
身份证件
ID chips.
真不巧 我们忘带了
Funny thing, we don't have 'em.
我们有这个
We have this.
精炼超空间燃料
Refined hyperfuel.
它至少值八百个信用点
It's worth at least 800 credits, maybe more.
持有这个东西是违法的
You could be detained just for having that.
你为什么要这么严肃呢
What good would that do anybody?
让我们过去就是你的了
Let us through, it's all yours.
把核芯素交给我
The coaxium, now.
让我们通过就给你
As we're going through, not before.
给她
Do it.
快给她
Just do it, do it.
别想跑了 琦拉 快进来
Not so fast, Qi'ra! Come on!
等等 快把门打开
Wait! Open the door!
警卫警卫 有人闯入
Security! Security, there has been a breach!
快把门打开
Open the door!
- 跑 快跑 跑 - 你们给我放开她
- Run! Run! - Get your hands off of her!
快跑
Run!
你们给我放开她
Get your hands off of her!
琦拉
Qi'ra!
快跑 汉 走啊
Run, Han! Go!
快走
Keep moving.
琦拉
Qi'ra!
快跑
Run!
涉事旅客已被抓捕
Traveler has been apprehended.
琦拉 我会回来的 我会回来的
Qi'ra, I'll come back! I'll come back!
全体注意 有人闯入
All units, there has been a breach.
还有一名非法旅客闯入了检查站
Another unauthorized traveler made it through the gate.
有人闯过关卡 去那边搜索
One got through the gate! Look over there!
有人闯过了检查站
Someone got through the checkpoint.
盯紧那道门 是 长官
Keep an eye on that gate. Yes, sir.
没有买票不能过去
Can't let you through without a ticket.
嘿 等等
Hey, wait!
跟我们走一趟
- Hey! - Come with us.
他就在这里 继续找
He's still out there. Keep looking.
那边那个 站住
You there, stop!
- 身份证给我看一下 - 求求你 不要
- Show me some identification. - Please. Please. No, no!
不要反抗
Do not resist.
投身伟大的事业 加入帝国
Be a part of something. Join the Empire.
探索新世界 学习宝贵的技能
Explore new worlds. Learn valuable skills.
给银河系带来秩序和稳定
Bring order and unity to the galaxy!
投身伟大的事业 加入帝国
Be a part of something. Join the Empire.
飞行员是在这里报名吧
This is where I sign up to be a pilot, right?
你可以申请加入帝国海军
If you apply for the Imperial Navy,
大多数新兵会加入陆军
but most recruits go into the infantry.
我要当飞行员 成为银河系最棒的飞行员
I'm gonna be a pilot. Best in the galaxy.
你过来 跟我们来一下
You there, come with us.
什么 我吗
Who, me?
我们要问你一些问题
We have a few questions to ask you.
需要多久才能毕业
How long is that gonna take?
那要看你能不能服从命令
Depends on how good you are at following orders.
你想飞到哪里去呀
Why, have you got somewhere to be?
回到这 越快越好
Yeah, back here, as soon as I can.
很少听到人这么说 你叫什么 孩子
Don't hear that much. What's your name, son?
汉
Han.
汉 你姓什么
Han what?
你的家人呢
Who are your people?
我没有家人 就我一个
I don't have people. I'm alone.
汉......
Han...
Solo也有孤身一人的意思
索罗
Solo.
通过了
Approved.
搭乘83号运输船 前往卡里达海军学校
Proceed to transport ID 83 for the Naval Academy at Carida.
祝你好运 汉·索罗
Good luck, Han Solo.
很快你就能当上飞行员了
We'll have you flying in no time.
三年后
帝国现在需要你 前进 士兵们
Your Empire needs you. Troopers forward!
索罗 起来 我们很快就到了
Solo, get up! We're almost there!
快到哪儿了 我们要去哪儿
Almost where? Where are we going?
只要越过最后一道山脊 胜利就...
Just over that last ridge. Victory is...
我的腿 我的腿
My legs! My leg!
嘿 贝克特 你说来这
Hey, Beckett, you said we were here
要干一票速战速决的
to pull a quick job.
- 是啊 - 这哪里是速战速决
- Yeah. - Well, this ain't a quick job!
这是持久战
It's a war!
你总是这么多废话
It's always something with you.
我们的目标是夺下步行机运输船
AT-hauler. That's what we came for.
前线指挥部一定是在这边
Forward operations must be this way.
没错 但少校说我们应该走这边
They are, but the major said we're supposed to go that way!
是啊 走那边送死吧
Yeah, go that way and die!
你说的对 少校已经死了
That's exactly what happened to the major!
现在谁是最高指挥官
Who's the ranking officer now?
是你 上尉
You are, Captain.
他说的没错呢
He's got you there.
有什么计划 贝克特上尉
So what's the plan, Captain Beckett?
瓦尔 你带里奥和这四个泥腿子包抄左翼
Val, you take Rio and these four mud skulls flank left.
我带上这个大嘴巴
I'll take this mouthy scooch
绕道右翼 然后...
and we'll go around to the right
没准我们运气好
and maybe we'll get lucky.
我们才不需要运气呢
Luck's got nothin' to do with it.
等等 一个问题 就一个问题
Wait! One question!
- 想活命吗 吉祥物 - 当然想了
- You wanna live, sparky? - Very much.
那就闭嘴 听从上尉的命令就行
Then shut up and do what your captain tells you.
我们冲
Let's go!
上尉
Captain.
T-15 报废了 我们走进去
T-15s are down. We walk from here.
上尉
Captain.
我是汉
I'm Han.
没兴趣听你介绍
Nobody cares.
刚才谢谢您 上尉
Thanks for your help back there.
你也不错
You did all right.
我接受过空战训练 所以...
I was trained in aerial combat...
想听我的建议吗
You want some advice?
赶紧离开这个鬼地方
Get the hell away from here.
不管去哪 越快越好
Any way you can, as fast as you can.
你指挥哪个连队
What company do you command?
跟你有什么关系么
None of your business company.
我们满员了
And we're full up.
当好你的兵 孩子
Stick to soldiering, kid.
别跟着我们
You don't want any part of this.
等等 兄弟们
Hang on, guys!
注意
Attention!
三小时后我们出发前往南部沼泽
In three hours, we move out for the southern marshlands.
我需要一只十人先锋队
I want an advance party of ten men.
真棒 又能吃土了
Great, more mud.
你说什么
What was that?
我只是在想我们的目标是什么 上尉
Just wondering what our objective is, Lieutenant.
为银河系带来和平与繁荣
Bring peace and prosperity to the galaxy,
建立忠于皇帝的新政权
install a regime loyal to the Emperor,
消灭敌对势力
and eradicate the hostiles.
这里是他们的星球 我们才是敌人
It's their planet, we're the hostiles.
你有什么意见么 士兵
You got a problem, trooper?
没意见 长官
No problem, sir.
全体出发
Moving out.
向南部沼泽 全体出发
To the southern marshlands! Move out!
执行命令 出发
You heard 'em! Let's move out!
嗯 看起来他们每半小时
Mmm. Looks like they're running sorties
出动一次
every 30 minutes.
是呀 我们可以解决警戒线上的卫兵
Yeah, I can take out the guards at the perimeter,
信号兵 飞行员
signalman, pilot.
见鬼 都解决了吧
Hell, I'll just take 'em all out.
你们在看什么
What are we looking at?
你小子怎么有
You have a talent for sticking your nose in
多管闲事的习惯
where it doesn't belong.
我想不注意到都难
I just couldn't help but notice
我看你们穿着满是激光枪弹孔的军装
you're wearing a uniform pock-full of laser burns.
你们要么是刀枪不入
So either you heal real quick
要么就是穿着从死人身上扒下来的军装
or you stole it off a dead man.
你们不是帝国士兵
You're not Imperial Army.
你们像是偷军火的
You're thieves here to steal equipment
我要入伙
for a job and I want in.
- 我们崩了他算了 - 不
- Well, now we gotta shoot him. - No.
拧断脖子更干脆一些
Snap his neck. It's less mess.
或者你们带我走
Or you take me with you.
我从小就在克雷利亚星球的街头坑蒙拐骗
Look, I came up running scams on the streets of Corellia.
我十岁就开始偷AV-21
I was boosting AV-21s when I was ten.
我会开车 开飞船
I'm a driver, a flyer,
而且你自己也跟我说过 我得离开这 对吧
and hey, you said yourself. I gotta get outta here. Right?
这么棒的飞行员这么下来趟泥水了
What's a fancy flyboy doing down in the mud?
这个 因为我思想独立
I got kicked out of the Imperial Academy
所以被帝国飞行学院开除了
for having a mind of my own.
但我可是个很不错的飞行员 我要回到我的故乡
But I am a great pilot. And I gotta get home.
这家伙疯了 谁会想回克雷利亚啊
This guy is nuts. No one goes back to Corellia.
我回那自有我的原因
I got a reason.
我们有很棒的飞行员了
We've already got a great pilot.
这个阿迪尼亚人
The Ardennian.
阿迪尼亚人 你不想活了吗
Ardennian? You got a lot of nerve, pal.
我是一名帝国士兵
I'm an Imperial trooper.
真的吗 你屁股上
Oh, really? A couple of your arms
长了两只胳膊
popped out of your butt
把裤子撑长这么大 士兵
and hiked up your pants, trooper.
胡扯
Oh, yeah?
听着 无论如何我要回克雷利亚
Look, I'll do whatever it takes to get back to Corellia.
我等不起了
I've already been away too long.
给个机会 谢谢您 长官
Just give me a shot.
等等  等等
Whoa. Hold it.
好吧 如果您对我没什么兴趣
Well, if you're not interested in me,
那中尉应该会对你非常感兴趣
I think the lieutenant might be very interested in you.
你威胁我
Blackmail.
中尉
Lieutenant.
上尉
Captain.
中尉 我们逮捕了一名逃兵
Lieutenant, we have apprehended a deserter.
把他带走
Take him.
我说 等一下
Wait.
我就知道 你小子不是个好东西
I should've known. This one's a troublemaker.
他还是个骗子 他说的话可别信
And a liar. Don't believe anything he says.
- 别丢下我 - 快点带走
- Don't go anywhere without me. - All right, let's go.
把他喂野兽
Feed him to the beast.
野兽 这有野兽吗
The beast? Wait, there's a beast?
- 等等 - 快走
- Hold on! - Move it!
那家伙是冒名顶替的
Listen, that guy's not even an officer. All right?
- 他在说谎 - 闭嘴
- He was lying! - Quiet!
我懒得管
Don't care.
有三天没喂他了
Haven't fed him in three days.
有好看的了
Should be fun.
大个子
Oh! Hey! Hey, big fella.
冷静一点 放松
Just calm down. Take it easy.
咱俩是一伙的
We're on the same side.
想吃点什么
You like treats?
救命 让我离开这
Help! Let me out of here!
让我离开这
Let me out of here!
抓住你了
A-ha! Gotcha!
感觉越来越精彩啊
Ah, this was just getting good.
它杀得太快了 对
- He killed him too fast. - Yeah!
慢点杀他
Kill him slower.
等等等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
等等......
Wait! Wait!
我会说一点伍基话
Yeah, I speak a little.
你听我说...
Now just listen to me, you...
对对对
Yes, yes!
不不不
No, no, no, no!
来吧
Do it!
来啊
Come on.
不
Oh, no!
赌十个信用点 他活不过一分钟
Ten credits, he doesn't last another minute.
让我离开这里
Let me out of here!
我实在是受不了了
I can't take it anymore!
不 住手  求你了
- Oh, no! Stop, please! - That's it. Get him!
你没劲了 你这肮脏的卡西克挤奶工
You tired, you mangy Kashyyykian moof-milker?
听我的 没错吧
See what happens when you listen to me?
你要干什么
Hey, what are you doing?
跟我来
Follow me!
等等过来
Wait, wait.
听我说 听我说
Come here. Listen to me.
你不明白
You don't understand, okay?
我有一群好朋友
I have some very good friends
在那个机场等我
waiting for me at that airfield.
他们马上要走了
They're leaving right now.
离开这里就靠他们了
That's our one way off this mud ball.
如果你想活命我们走那边
If you wanna live, we go that way.
然后你爱去哪去哪 我不管
After that, you go whichever way you want, I don't care!
但是现在 快往那边走
But right now, that's the way you go!
相信我
Trust me!
瓦尔 我们走
Val, let's go!
他们穿这玩意是怎么呼吸的 太闷了
How do they breathe in these suits? It's so stuffy!
怪不得他们飞行技术的那么烂
No wonder they're such lousy pilots.
没法转头 没法呼吸
You can't turn your head, you can't breathe,
听不到队友说什么
you can't hear each other!
活见鬼了
I'll be damned.
看谁回来了
Hey, look who's back!
简直难以置信
Unbelievable!
等等
Wait!
等一下
那是一个伍基人吗 不可思议
Whoa, is that a Wookiee? Incredible!
实话实说
I'll say it, I don't care.
我开始喜欢这孩子了
This kid's growing on me.
等等
Wait!
干这种活
You know, we could always use
多几个帮手总会有用的
some muscle on a job like this.
别打这主意
Don't even think about it!
我跟你讲 躺在伍基人的膝盖上睡觉
I'm telling you, you will never have a deeper sleep
是件非常惬意的事情
than curled up in a Wookiee's lap.
我跟你说过了
I told you!
非常好的朋友
Very good friends!
这种事情不能一个一个来吗
We couldn't have done this maybe, like, one at a time?
真得感谢你帮我离开那里
Thanks for helping me get outta there.
都是因为我 他们才带上你
No, they only took you because of me.
我跟他们做了一笔非常棒的交易
I got us a real sweet deal here.
只要跟他们一起干上一票
We do this one job with them,
我们赚上一大笔钱
we make some real money,
然后我们就自由了
and then we're free.
你多久没有享受过自由了
When's the last time you could say that?
我也很久没自由过了
Been a while for me, too.
那么你叫什么名字
So what's your name, anyway?
丘巴卡
Chewbacca?
这个名字...我得给你起个外号
All right, well, you're gonna need a nickname,
不然喊你的名字太麻烦了
'cause I ain't saying that every time.
他来了 你看一下
Here it comes. Take a look.
列车走到塔和桥中间的时候 我们就动手
We hit the Conveyex between the tower and the bridge.
里奥送我们上去 我们拆下货箱
Rio drops us in, we separate the payload container,
把它吊在步行运输机上 然后...
cable it up to the AT-hauler and then...
里奥干扰他们的报警信号
Rio jams their distress signal.
我炸毁桥
I blow the bridge,
然后从轨道上把车厢吊走
the container slides right off the track
我们一走了之
and we sail away.
如果触发报警信号
You trip that security beam,
激活了蝮蛇机器人
wake up those Vipers,
那情况就会变得非常危险
it's liable to get real spicy, real fast.
你需要担心的人可不是我
Well, I'm not the one you should be worried about.
恩菲斯·内斯特
Enfys Nest.
恩菲斯·奈斯特是谁
What's an Enfys Nest?
我跟你说过 我们干的这一票
I told you, we're way ahead
不会有人插手的
of the competition on this one.
恩菲斯·内斯特甚至不知道
There's no way Enfys Nest
这批货运输的消息
even knows about this shipment.
只有我那边的人知道这消息
Only my guy has the intel.
那你的人最好别出差错
Well, you better be right. Yeah?
因为有的时候
Because sometimes, you put your faith
你也会看错人
in the wrong people.
我们的未来都压在这一票上
Our whole future depends on this one score
你却带上两个生手
and you bring in amateurs.
可能你没注意到
In case you hadn't noticed,
我们真的缺人手
we're a little shorthanded.
那就去找啊
So we get who we need.
扎恩姐妹 或者是博斯克 你偏不找他们
The Xan sisters, or Bossk.
你把咱俩的命放在
But, no, instead you're putting our lives
两个傻瓜的手上
in the hands of morons.
你俩傻吗
You guys morons?
不
No!
- 听见了 不 - 我们俩一点不傻
- No. See? - We're not morons.
我一直在等待一个这样的机会
Look, I waited a long time for a shot like this.
我不会搞砸的
I'm not about to screw it up, all right?
哦 好了 瓦尔
Oh, come on, Val!
你看他多真诚啊
He looks so sincere.
再说拒绝
Plus, have you ever tried to disinvite
一个伍基人
a Wookiee to anything?
后果可一点都不好
Not a good idea!
这一点也不好笑
This is not funny!
听着 直觉告诉我 他们两个靠得住
Look, now, I have great instincts about these guys.
再说了 我们还有其他选择吗
And, besides, do you see any other options?
希望你自己心里有数
I just hope you know what you're doing.
我很清楚我为什么要这么做
Yeah, I know exactly what I'm doing and why.
我们要把债还清
We're gonna clear our debts,
返回格利安塞姆
go back to Glee Anselm,
我要学会弹梵弦琴
and I'm finally gonna learn how to play that valachord.
哦 宝贝儿 你永远也学不会弹梵弦琴
Babe, you're never gonna learn how to play the valachord.
说的对 你是个音痴
She's right. You are tone-deaf.
你遇到过什么伤心事 小飞哥
So what's your sob story, flyboy?
你问我么
Who, me?
我看的出你心里有事
You're after something, I know the look.
是不是要报仇
What is it? Revenge?
不 不是报仇
No, it's not revenge.
你看他
Look at him.
肯定是因为一个姑娘
If it's anything, it's a girl.
哦 姑娘
Oh, a girl!
跟我们讲讲她 汉 她人怎么样
Tell us about the girl, Han. Is she nice?
她有尖尖的牙吗
Does she have sharp teeth?
以前有那么一个女孩
There was a girl.
当时我逃出来了 而她没有
But I got out, she didn't.
我发誓要成为一名飞行员
I swore to myself I'd become a pilot,
弄艘船
get a ship,
回去找到她
go back and find her.
干完这票后就去找她
That's what I'm gonna do right after this job.
你怎么知道她还呆在那儿
How you know she'll still be there?
我就是知道
I just know.
我可不想被任何人束缚住
Personally, I refuse to be tied down
追我的人可多着呢
by anyone, though many have tried.
得了吧 里奥 别逗了
Come on, Rio. You don't fool me.
人都需要有个伴
Everybody needs somebody.
即便是你这个老骗子也不例外
Even a broken down old crook like this one.
你分到钱后 打算干嘛去
How about you? What are you gonna do with your share?
他说什么
What was he saying?
他说伍基人
He said the Wookiees were enslaved
被帝国奴役 远离家乡
by the Empire, taken off Kashyyyk.
他好像在寻找他的…
He's searching for his, uh...
我不知道是他说的是部落还是家人
I don't know if he said tribe or family.
有区别吗
What's the difference?
教我怎么做
Show me how to do that.
你唯一需要学会的是…
The only thing you need to learn to do
按我说的去做
is do what I say when I say it.
明天这个时候
And this time tomorrow,
你就有足够的钱
you'll have more than enough
买一艘飞船了
to buy your own ship.
现在开始计时
Starting the clock.
正在干扰信号 距离大桥9.6
Jamming their signal. 9.6 to the bridge.
拿出你们的真本事来 伙计们
Let's find out how good we really are, folks.
我没事儿
I'm fine!
瓦尔 你那边情况如何
Val, how's it going up there?
一切顺利
Never better.
核芯素
Coaxium.
足够一支舰队用的
Enough to power a fleet!
也可以把我们炸的粉身碎骨
Or blow us all straight to hell!
好的 告诉我
All right, talk to me.
今天是好日子吗
Is it a good day?
堪称完美
It's a great day!
你生命最好的一天 贪心鬼
Best day of your life, my grabby friend!
难说 你从没有在阿迪尼亚
I don't know, you've never been
享受过迈诺克烧烤
to a Mynock roast on Ardennia.
那才绝呢
It's nuts!
他们来了
Here they come!
断开车厢连接器
Get down to the couplers!
里奥 后撤
Rio, fall back!
他们反应还挺快的
Well, that didn't take 'em long.
丘伊
Chewie!
你没事儿吧
You all right?
你差点就挂了 兄弟
Little close there, buddy!
汉 怎么还没好
Han, what's the holdup?
我们一起来
All right, together.
用力
Now!
好了
All right!
他们解开一边儿了 你在哪儿呢 伙计
They got one uncoupled. Where are you, buddy?
我正在规划退休生活
Just up here planning my retirement.
在考虑某个温暖又不太热的地方
Thinking about opening a cantina
开个小酒馆呢
somewhere warm but not too warm, you know?
快把绳索放出来
Lowering the winch cables now!
我就知道 我早说了 贝克特
I knew it! I told him! Beckett!
他来了
He's coming!
见鬼 这回要被她唠叨个没完了
Damn it! I'm never gonna hear the end of this!
那是谁
Who's that?
恩菲斯·内斯特
Enfys Nest!
土匪 海盗
Marauders, pirates.
想来从我们嘴里抢吃的
Come to snake the score from under us.
准备发射缆绳
Ready your harpoons.
冲上去
Move in.
等一下 我这里有位不速之客
Hang on! I got an uninvited guest.
从我的船里滚出去
Get off of my ship!
你还好吗 兄弟
You still with us, brother?
噢 我还好
Yeah, I'm okay.
就是一边的肩膀划破了 没什么
Just nicked one of my shoulders. It's nothing.
他一点都不好
He's not okay.
丘伊
Chewie!
得靠你一个人解开这边了
You gotta uncouple this one on your own!
汉
Han!
我知道了
I'm on it!
瓦尔
Val!
眼睛睁大点 我们触发了一个传感器
Keep your eyes open. We just tripped a sensor.
蝮蛇机器人朝你们去了
Viper droids headed your way!
里奥
Rio?
嗯 情况不妙
Yeah, it looks worse than it is.
得包扎一下
Just gotta patch it up.
也许得小睡一会
Maybe rest my eyes for a minute.
够了 我自己来
Enough! I'm going in.
你没撒谎 小伙子
You weren't lying, kid.
技术真不赖
You're a hell of a pilot.
里奥 伙计 挺住
Rio, stay with me, buddy.
贝克特 我们有一根缆绳断了
Beckett, we just lost a cable!
距离大桥2.1
2.1 to the bridge!
一个人死真没劲 小伙子
It's no good to die alone, kid.
瓦尔说得对
Val was right.
里奥
Rio?
贝克特 距离大桥0.8
Beckett, we're .8 from the bridge!
瓦尔还在轨道上
Val's still on the track!
瓦尔你快离开那座桥
Val, you gotta get off that bridge!
我们来了
We're here!
它们把我困在这了
They got me pinned!
我得在这里动手了
I'm gonna have to finish the job from right here.
什么
What?
我不虚此生 宝贝
It's been a ride, babe.
跟你在一起的日子是我最珍贵的一段时光
And I wouldn't trade it for anything.
瓦尔
Val!
不
No!
丘伊 快
Chewie, now!
贝克特 我拉不过他们
Beckett, I can't pull it away from 'em.
他们会放手的 你尽管飞
They'll let go, you fly straight!
快松开缆绳
Release your cables
要不然就要死了
or die!
我们太近了
We're too close.
我得松开
I gotta release.
照我说的做 汉
You do what I tell you, Han!
丘伊 抓住缆绳
Chewie, grab the line!
不许断开
Don't you do it!
汉
Han!
你这个懦夫
You coward!
你干什么
What the hell?
你不听话 也不服从命令
You don't listen and you can't follow orders!
你知不知道你都干了什么
You have any idea what you've done?
偷这批货不是为了我们自己
We were not stealing for ourselves,
我们是受雇于血红黎明的
we were hired by Crimson Dawn.
血红黎明
Crimson Dawn?
我们欠了他们100千克的精炼核芯素
Now we owe them 100 keys of refined coaxium.
要是他们发现我们没把东西弄到手
When they find out we don't got it,
就会杀了我们
they're gonna kill us.
对
Right.
赶紧逃
We run.
我已经是个逃兵了 没什么区别了
I'm already a deserter. What's the difference?
你说区别
The difference
如果你是一名逃兵
is the Empire doesn't send out
帝国可不会派出一队杀手
a team of enforcers to hunt you down
去追杀你
when you're a deserter.
可德赖登·沃斯会
Dryden Vos will.
你知道有人悬赏
You have any idea what it's like
要你的命是什么感觉吗
to live with a price on your head?
你唯一能做的就是请罪
The only thing to do is to go to them.
也许我能想个办法来补偿他
Maybe I can find some way to make it up to him.
那就按你说的来
Then that's what we do.
不好吧
No.
他们认识我 不认识你
He knows me, not you.
如果你跟着我一起过去
If you come with me
一旦露面
and show your face,
哪怕他们留你一命
if they don't kill you,
你这辈子就得一直干这行了
you're in this life for good.
如果你能想个办法解决这件事
You find some way to square this,
我们还能拿到钱吗
we still get our money?
也许吧
Maybe.
那我们就值得为之冒险
For me, it's worth the risk.
你觉得呢
How about you?
他同意了
That's yes.
抱歉 我刚打了你一拳
Sorry I punched your face.
挨揍这种事对我来说是家常便饭了
Happens more often than you think.
我们上去之后
So when we get up there,
德赖登·沃斯就在伊普索堡等我们么
Dryden Vos is waiting for us at Fort Ypso?
他的船就在附近
Nearby, on his yacht.
你知道船在哪吗
You're gonna know how to find it?
那根本不成问题
That won't be a problem.
把你们的武器交出来
I'll need to check your weapons.
我就剩这一件武器了
That's all I got left.
我来找德赖登 他在等着见我
I'm here to see Dryden. He's expecting me.
他马上来见你
He'll be with you shortly.
他和区域总督的会面刚刚结束
He's just finishing with the regional governor.
打扰 长官
Excuse me, sir.
说
Yes.
贝克特到了
- Beckett has arrived. - Oh.
把这放我办公室 待会可能要用
Put this in my office. I might be needing it later.
我发什么火嘛 真是的
I get all worked up. Silly.
这可是宴会 应该开心一点
It's a party.
这里的人可不是你朋友
These people are not your friends
你永远都不可能成为他们的朋友 所以别跟任何人说话
and they're never gonna be, so don't talk to any of 'em.
所以眼睛也别乱瞟
Don't look at anybody,
把头低下看路
just keep your eyes down.
我得去喝一杯
I might get a drink.
不 好吧 随便
No, yeah, whatever.
丘伊 你能不能...
Chewie, would you please...
琦拉 你怎么在这
Qi'ra, what are you doing here?
我在这工作
I work here.
你怎么在这
What's your excuse?
我 我
My... I...
琦 琦拉...我...
Qi'ra, I was...
我正想着回去找你呢
I was coming back for you.
那些日子都过去了 汉
It's in the past, Han.
我可不这么想
Not for me.
我来到这
The only reason I'm here,
就是想做份工作赚一点钱
I was doing this job, get a little money
然后回克雷利亚去找你
and then I was gonna come back to Corellia and find you.
现在你不必了
Well, now you don't have to.
我就站在你面前
I'm right in front of you.
那天
That day...
有时候我经常在想
Sometimes, a lot of times, I think...
如果你留下...
If you'd have stayed,
他们会杀了你的
they would've killed you.
你能逃走 我很高兴
I'm glad you got out.
你是怎么脱身的
How did you get out?
我没有脱身
I didn't.
你气色不错
You look good.
有一点不修边幅
A little rough around the edges,
但挺精神
but good.
你也是
You too.
谢谢 奥蒂莉
Thank you, Ottilie.
你在关注多克·昂达吗
Have you been attentive to Dok-Ondar?
当然
Very.
我们为什么举杯呢
What should we drink to?
不管为什么 先喝两杯在说
Let's drink two and see where it goes.
你弄到那艘可以让我们远走高飞的船了吗
Did you ever get that ship we were going to fly away on?
快了 也差不多
Yeah. Sort of.
马上吧 所以我来这儿是准备...
About to. That's why I'm here.
我正在做一笔
I'm working on a...
大买卖
Very big deal.
有多大
How big?
非常大
Enormous.
真的假的 那你什么时候搞定这笔大买卖
Really? And when are you going to close this enormous deal?
可能下一秒就搞定了
Any minute.
我经常想起你
I thought about you a lot.
你在某个地方冒险
Off somewhere, some adventure.
我想像自己在你身边 那样总能让我...
I imagined myself with you. It always made me...
- 什么 - 嘿
- What? - Hey.
我怎么跟你说的
What did I say?
听着 我不可能一直低着头
Look, I can't keep my eyes down the whole time.
那样我会撞上东西的
I'm gonna bump into something.
我说别跟任何人说话 你怎么...
But I told you not to talk to anyone.
贝克特
Beckett.
等等 你们在一起做事
Wait. You two work together?
- 对 - 托拜厄斯
- Yeah. - Tobias!
德赖登
Dryden.
你好吗 有没有受伤
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
没有 我很好
No, I'm fine.
瓦尔的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear about Val.
谢谢你 但是...
Yeah, I appreciate that.
我们没想到会...
But there was no way we could've anticipated...
我想我们俩没见过面吧
I don't believe we've been introduced.
对 这是汉·索罗和丘巴卡
Yeah. This is Han Solo and Chewbacca.
他们是跟我一起的
They're with me.
我是德赖登·沃斯
I'm Dryden Vos.
看来你们已经见过我的高级助理了...
I see you've already met my top lieutenant.
汉和我一起在科雷利亚长大
Han and I grew up together on Corellia.
一个窝出来的
Oh, fellow scrumrat.
我钦佩那些那些靠自己爬出下水道的人
I admire anyone who can crawl their way out of the sewer.
尤其是像科雷利亚那样肮脏的下水道
Especially, a sewer as putrid as Corellia.
臭烘烘的 我说的对吧
The stench, am I right?
很高兴见到你
Well, it's good to have you.
欢迎
Welcome.
你也是 丘巴卡 欢迎
And you, too, Chewbacca, welcome.
好了 我们少吃点儿 多喝点儿
All right, let's eat a little, drink a lot,
然后私下聊聊
and talk privately.
他们只是朋友
We're just friends, all right?
你太敏感了
You're touchy.
贝克特 你给我出了一个大难题
Beckett, you have put me in a terrible position.
我知道 德赖登 我非常抱歉
I know, Dryden, and I am sorry.
你很抱歉
You're sorry?
德赖登 事情很复杂
Dryden, there were complications.
有些原因
There were factors.
恩菲斯·内斯特 一直都在找我们的麻烦
Enfys Nest has been a constant irritation forever.
你应该能预料到这个情况的
It's one you should've anticipated,
你应该能解决这个的
it's one you should've dealt with.
我知道我犯了个错误
Trust me, I know I made a mistake,
但是你雇我的时候
but when you hired me, you told me
你跟我说没有其他人知道
no one else had this information...
够了
Test me!
你敢再啰嗦一个字试试看
Test me one more time, you'll see what happens.
我认为德赖登想说的是
I think what Dryden is trying to say
我们没兴趣知道 你为什么现在没拿到货
is that we're not interested in why you don't have it.
对 我不感兴趣
No, I'm not interested.
我一点儿都不感兴趣
I'm not interested at all.
德赖登
Dryden,
我该怎么做才能挽回这一切
what can I do to make this right?
挽回这一切
"Make this right?"
没什么可以挽回的
There is no making this right.
你知道我老板是谁
You know who I answer to
你也知道他对我有什么期待
and you know what he'll expect of me.
他会说 你必须承担后果
He'll say, "There have to be consequences."
所以接下来我需要你做一件事
So here's what I need you to do for me.
我需要你给我一个...
I need you to give me a reason
不杀你们的理由
not to kill you all.
因为我一定会对你作出补偿
Because I will make it up to you.
不 怎么补 你怎么补偿我
No, no, no. How?
我会遵守之前的约定
How will you make it up to me?
把货交给你
By delivering exactly what was promised.
还是100千克精炼核芯素吗
100 k-grams of refined coaxium?
是的 我们会从其它的地方给你偷来
Yes. We will simply steal it from somewhere else.
从什么地方
From where?
除了帝国仓库
You'll be hard pushed to find that
你很难在其他地方找到核芯素
anywhere outside an Imperial vault.
斯卡里夫 或者仁慈岛
Scarif. Maybe Mercy Island.
那是不可能的
That's impossible.
所以我们想想其它办法
So, let's come up with some other options.
其它能让我们...
Other ideas that we might...
没有精炼的行不行
What about unrefined?
唯一已知的 不稳定核芯素来源
Well, the only known source of astatic coaxium
是科舍尔星球香料矿的地下裂缝
is a fissure vent beneath the spice mines on Kessel.
对 我想的就是这里
Yeah. That's the one I was thinking of.
那个来源地非常棒
That's a very, very good one.
但是科舍尔由派克人控制着
But see, the Pykes control Kessel.
血红黎明与派克人
Crimson Dawn maintains
保持着脆弱的同盟关系
a fragile alliance with the Pykes.
我不能破坏这关系
It's one that I can't jeopardize
不然就会引起全面的帮派冲突
without risking an all-out war with the Syndicates,
所以听着 先生们 我绝不会同意
and that, gentlemen, I will not do.
那么如果没有其他提议 我们的谈话到此为止
So, if that's all you have, I think we're done here.
我们还有话要说
Not all we have.
我们跟派克人可没有同盟关系
We don't have any alliance with the Pykes.
对 没人知道我们是为你效力的
Right, so nobody is gonna know we're working for you.
有可能成功么
Possible?
有风险
It's risky.
一旦将没加工的核芯素取出仓库
As soon as the raw coaxium is removed from the vault,
它会变得不稳定
it starts to destabilize,
所以除非
so unless...
除非
Unless...
除非...
配合一下嘛
Work with me here.
除非你能找个地方
Unless you could find somewhere
马上对它进行精炼
to get it processed fast.
那个...
Well...
他说萨瓦林
He's saying Savareen?
萨瓦林
Savareen.
对 那儿有一个老旧的精炼厂
Yeah, it's an old refinery there
那地方不受帝国的管辖
and it's not under Imperial jurisdiction.
琦拉说得对
But Qi'ra's right.
在你们抵达前储藏罐就会爆炸 所以...
The canisters will explode before you get there,
你们需要 一艘非常快的船
so you'd need an incredibly fast ship
和一流的飞行员
and a brilliant pilot.
我们会找到船的
We'll find a ship.
飞行员已经有了
We've already got the pilot.
他很傲慢 也很有野心
He is arrogant and he's hungry.
你怎么看 亲爱的
So what do you think, my dear?
你觉得你的这位朋友 能胜任这次任务吗
You think your friend here can do what needs to be done?
是的 我觉得他可以
Yes, I believe he can.
这是个好消息
Well, that is good news,
因为你要跟着他
because you're going with him
确保他做到
to see that he does.
好吗
All right?
没问题
Of course.
好的
All right.
我们萨瓦林见
I'll see you all on Savareen.
萨瓦林见
Savareen it is.
- 我很看好这个方案 - 我也是
- I feel great about this plan. - Me, too.
我们应该常聊聊 很有意思
We should do this again. It's been fun.
是啊
Great.
对了 还有一件事儿
Oh, just one more thing.
如果你们再让我失望
If you do fail me again,
那就没办法了
we'll all be out of options.
对吧
Right?
你放心吧
We won't.
一切进行得挺顺利的
So, I thought that went really well.
我们尽量快点解决这件事
Let's get this done as quick and as clean as possible.
你们需要什么
What do you need?
装备我有办法弄来
I can scrounge up the gear.
你能弄到船吗
Do you got a line on a ship?
我认识一个人
I know a guy.
我知道能去哪儿找到他
And I know just where to find him.
不是很有希望 但值得一试
It's a long shot, but it's worth a try.
他是最厉害的走私犯
He's the best smuggler around.
他从帝国的追捕中逃脱的次数
He's slipped through the Empire's fingers
比任何走私犯都要多
more times than anyone else.
他很有魅力
He's attractive, too.
他久经世故
Sophisticated,
品味超凡 而且风流倜傥
with impeccable taste and... Charisma.
更不用说他那惊人的...
Not to mention his prodigious...
知道了
We get it.
不过他现在已经金盆洗手了 他说自己是个职业玩家
But he's retired. Says he's a sportsman now.
我们只需要他的船
All we need is his ship.
他的船从不外借
Well, he'll never part with it.
他爱死那艘船了
He loves that ship.
那是他
He won it
玩萨巴卡牌赢来的
playing Sabacc.
那么问题来了
And there's the rub, right?
我怎么知道她是个帝国间谍
How was I supposed to know she was an Imperial spy?
我以为她爱我呢
I thought she loved me.
就是那家伙
That's the guy, huh?
是个有趣的家伙
An interesting style.
我同意
I'll say.
你说他的船是赢来的
You say he won his ship?
你的表情出卖了你 我决定跟你了
You have an awful Sabacc face. I'm gonna call it.
我能赢他 我跟他赌
I can take him. Let me at him.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
汉 这群人是职业赌徒
Han, these guys are serious gamblers.
我也挺专业的 给我点赌注
I'm serious. Stake me.
别听他瞎说
Don't listen to him.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
各位让我赢一局如何
You see, how'd you guys let me beat you on that one?
来吧
Come on.
今天没有骗子只有玩家
There's no liars in this game, just players.
这个座位没人吧
Is this seat taken?
没人坐就是没人 朋友
If nobody's in the seat, then it ain't taken, friend.
这就是...斯巴克
So this is, uh, Sabacc?
萨巴卡
Sabacc.
萨巴卡 对
Sabacc. Got it.
你玩过吗
You play it before?
玩过几次
A couple times, yeah.
我是兰多·卡瑞辛船长
Captain Lando Calrissian.
汉·索罗
Han Solo.
看来你今天手气不错呀
Looks like you're having a good day.
我运气好
I'm a lucky guy.
我能问你个问题吗 卡瑞辛船长
Can I ask you a question, Captain Calrissian?
随便问 憨
Anything, Han.
我叫汉 不过没关系
That's "Han", but that's okay.
我听到过一些关于你的故事 想知道是不是真的
I heard a story about you. I was wondering if it's true.
你听到的所有关于我的故事 都是真的
Everything you've heard about me is true.
谢谢宝贝儿
Thanks, love.
你的船是玩牌赢来的吗
Did you win your ship playing cards?
我赢过很多东西
Oh, I've won a lot of things.
我在奥西恩星带赢过一颗亚热带卫星
I once won a subtropical moon in the Oseon Belt.
哇
Wow.
结果是个赔钱货
Turned out to be a real money pit.
你真行
I'm impressed.
要是我可不敢把
I don't think I'd have the nerve to gamble
自己喜欢的船拿来做赌注
with something I love as much as my ship.
- 是吗 - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
你开的是什么船
What do you fly?
VCX-100
VCX-100.
那可是艘好船 是吧 伙计们
That is a quality ship. Right, boys?
银河系最快的
It's the fastest in the galaxy,
银河系其他好船也不少
but there's a lot of great ships out there.
我觉得你的船肯定也很棒
I mean, I'm sure yours is very nice.
只是个代步工具呗
Gets me where I'm goin'.
新手好运
Beginner's luck.
玩的不错
Well played.
看看这次是什么
Let's see what we got here.
好牌呀
Oh, great hand!
抱歉各位 赢我 还差一点儿
Sorry, guys. Close, but not quite.
眼睛看自己的牌 伙计
Eyes on your own cards, buddy.
所有的眼睛
All of 'em.
看那儿 现在我看见你的了
There. Well, now I see yours.
说我吗 好 让我看看...
Oh, that's me? Okay, let's see...
抱歉 负二点
Sorry, minus two.
这游戏好玩儿
This game is fun.
好吧 这样如何
All right, how about this?
我跟你 并且加注
I'll see your bet and I'll raise you.
两千
2,000.
我跟两千
I'll see your 2,000
再加注
and I'll raise you
这些我全加上
however much this is.
汉
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Han.
悠着点儿
Slow down.
你该见好就收
You might wanna quit while you're ahead.
那你该见输就收喽
You might wanna quit while you're behind.
我喜欢这家伙
I like this kid.
你可真逗
You're adorable.
我是认真的
And I'm serious.
我跟你
And I'm calling.
你用什么跟
With what?
你的围巾
Your scarf?
可不对我的口味
Not my style.
用我的船
My ship.
赌你的船
Against your ship.
看看你有没有这个胆
Time to find out if you got the nerve.
放马过来
What the hell?
法杖顺子
Straight Staves.
你耍我 你可以
You played me. You're good.
- 是啊 - 太会玩儿了
- Yeah. - You're very good.
但还差一点儿
But not good enough.
满点萨巴克
Full Sabacc.
跟你说了见好就收
I told you to quit while you were ahead.
我请大家喝酒
Drinks on me!
对 没错
Yeah, that's right.
首先 他绝对不可能
First of all, there's no way
有那张绿牌
he could've had that green sylop.
绿牌都出过了
They'd all been played.
而且你的神奇船长
Also, your guy, Captain Wonderful,
吹班萨牛不打草稿
is so full of bantha crap...
我的VCX在哪儿呢
Where's my VCX?
现在不在这儿
I don't have it right here now.
目前它在维修厂
It's in the shop.
- 我正在做一些改装 - 兰多
- I'm getting some work done. - Lando.
琦拉
Qi'ra.
你真是光彩夺目 一如既往
You look phenomenal. As always.
因为我要来见你啊
Well, I knew I was gonna see you.
别碰我
Get off!
你跟他们在一起干吗
What are you doing with hairy and the boy?
- 不关你的事儿 别问 - 他们为我工作
- There's no need, none. - They work for me.
嗯 好帮手难找啊
Good help is hard to find, no?
我们其实是合作伙伴
We're more like partners.
真的
We are.
失陪一下
Excuse us.
听我说 之前我确定过了
Listen, last I checked,
我跟血红黎明 已经两清了
me and Crimson Dawn, we're squared away.
德赖登说了
Dryden said all is forgiven
我为他做完费卢西亚那票 就都一笔勾销
after I did the whole Felucia thing for him.
这是新买卖 我们要跑科舍尔航线
Yeah. New move, we're making the Kessel Run.
我们需要艘船
We need a ship.
你怎么不早说
Why didn't you just say so?
我以为你不干了
I thought you were retired.
我为你破例了
Circumstances change.
你要多少
How much?
科舍尔航线可不太好跑
The Kessel Run.
我要抽百分之五十
That's no easy spin. I'm gonna need half the take.
你想的美
Ridiculous.
嘘 小孩别插嘴
Grown-ups are talking.
百分之二十五
25%.
你是托拜厄斯·贝克特
You're Tobias Beckett.
你杀了奥拉·辛
You killed Aurra Sing.
就推了一下 她肯定是自己摔死的
Pushed her. Pretty sure the fall killed her.
你为银河系做了件好事 对我来说更是如此
You did the galaxy a favor that day. Me, especially.
我欠她一大笔钱
I owed her a lot of money.
为了表达我的感激之情
And as token of my gratitude,
这票我愿意只抽百分之四十
I'm willing to do this for 40%.
二十五
25.
那就百分之二十五
25% works.
不 简直无法接受
No! Unacceptable!
停止剥削机器人
Stop exploiting droids!
你们这些堕落的生物
You sloppy degenerate bios!
- 她真是没记性 - 你们不觉得羞耻吗
- She never learns. - Have you no shame?
谁
Who?
我的大副
My first mate.
这跟你有什么关系 快滚开
You got no business being here. Get out of here!
你怎么能容忍这种野蛮行为
How can you condone this savagery?
你 你 你们不应该这样做
You, you. You should not be doing this.
他们在利用你们取乐
They're using you for entertainment.
对 你们被洗脑了
Yeah. You've been neurowashed.
不要盲目的服从程序
Don't just blindly follow the program.
行使你们的自由意志
Exercise some free will!
离他远一点儿
Stay away from him!
他从来就没有这么好过
He's never had it so good.
哦 真的吗 那你跟我打一架呀 你这个傻大个
Oh, really? How about you have a go at me, ya lumpy brute.
那就来啊 来呀
Bring it on! Come on!
L3
L3!
机器人平等 我们是智慧生命
Droid rights! We are sentient!
我要关掉你的开关
I'm gonna flip your switch.
找得到算你赢
Good luck finding it.
L3
L3!
别理那个卑鄙小人
Let go of the mean man's face.
该走了
We're leaving.
他们这里都不招待机器人
They don't even serve our kind here.
快走
Now.
这些人是谁
Who are these guys?
送他们去科舍尔
We're taking them to Kessel.
你说什么
Oh, are we?
如果我不想去科舍尔呢
And what if I don't elect to go to Kessel?
别闹了行不行
Please don't start.
有本事清除我记忆呀
Or what, you'll have me wiped?
没有我你连黑峰站都到不了
You couldn't get from here to Black Spire without me.
还想跑科舍尔航线
Now you're gonna make the Kessel Run?
如果她不想驾驶 我愿意当你的副驾驶
If she doesn't wanna fly, I'll be your co-pilot.
- 我不介意的  - 不不不 不必了
- I don't mind. - No, no. It's okay.
她肯定会去的
She's definitely going.
为什么 因为你这物种天生就高我们一等是吗
Oh, why? Because you're my organic overlord?
因为我是你船长 你觉得这理由怎么样
Because I'm your captain, how about that?
我真想清除她的记忆
I actually would have her memory wiped,
但她的航线
but she's got the best damn
是银河系最全的
navigational database in the galaxy.
给你上一层全新的漆怎么样
Could use a fresh coat of paint, though!
兰多 我才不要呢 你可别把我惹火了
Landonis, you do not want to press that button with me.
这里经常有船被盗
You know, a lot of ships around here get boosted.
所以我平时都把船锁起来
So, I keep mine locked up.
你懂的 安全起见
You know, for safety.
L3 劳您大驾
L3, do you mind?
别看我
Look away.
你们这样我没法工作
I can't perform with you looking at me.
迁就一下吧
Please indulge her.
我能感觉到你们在看我
I can feel you looking at me.
我们这是在干嘛
What are we doing here?
他就是个骗子
This guy's a hustler.
我觉得他根本就没有船
I don't even think he's got a ship.
就算有
If he does, it's gonna be a piece of junk
也绝对是个垃圾货
if it's even here.
在这儿 我的心肝宝贝儿
There she is, my pride and joy.
千年隼号
The Millennium Falcon.
你还改装了一下
Looks like you had a little work done.
的确如此 汉
Indeed I have, Han.
开口处安装了一个逃生舱
Installed an escape pod in the mandible notch,
还有冲流阀 小吧台
alluvial dampers, a wet bar.
而且起落架上
And a fortified infraction
还安装了强化固定器
restraint on the landing gear.
看上去他们扣押了你的船 兰多
Looks to me like they impounded your ship, Lando.
什么 真是岂有此理
This is unbelievable!
看来
I'm definitely gonna have some words
我得找人投诉了
with someone about this.
你会拆除固定器吗
You must have experience with these, right?
我能拆掉它们
Yeah, I could take it off.
太棒了
Fantastic!
那你的抽成就要扣掉百分之五
Along with five percent off your cut.
给你百分之二十
You're down to 20.
我不喜欢这主意
I don't like it.
我不赞成
I don't agree with it.
但我接受
But I accept it.
你开始上道了 兰多
You're getting the hang of this, Lando.
是啊
Yeah.
来吧丘伊
Come on, Chewie.
展示一下你的伍基之力吧
Gonna need a little bit of that Wookiee oomph.
一切按计划进行 恩菲斯
Your plan is underway, Enfys.
我们安装了追踪器
We've attached the homing beacon.
这回他们跑不掉了
They won't elude us now.
很好
Good.
如果他们没死 我们就能坐享其成了
If they survive, they'll bring the prize to us.
这是一艘科雷利亚YT-1300
This is a Corellian YT-1300.
你懂得不少
Oh. You know your stuff.
我见过这个型号
I've been on one before.
我爸爸以前
My dad worked the line
在一条造船厂装配线上工作 后来丢了工作
at the CEC plant before he got laid off.
他造过这种船
He built these.
他一直想当驾驶员 但是...
He wanted to be a pilot, but...
你跟你爸关系好吗
You, uh, close with your old man?
不算好
Not really.
是吗 我也是
Yeah, me neither.
不过 我的妈妈
My mom, on the other hand,
是我见过最美的女人
most amazing woman I've ever known.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
把你骄傲的屁股从我的座位上移开
Get your presumptuous ass out of my seat!
我的骶骨枕骨电路卡住了
My sacral-occipital circuit is sticking.
等会儿你得再来一次
You're gonna have to do that thing again later.
好
Yeah.
好了 科舍尔航线已设定
All right, course to Kessel is set.
现在导入方位数据
Plugging coordinates in now.
手放在操纵杆上就行
Just keep your pinky on the yoke
别弄坏其他设备
and try not to mess anything up.
听你的 女士
Whatever you say, my lady.
提醒我什么时候跳跃
Just let me know when you're ready to jump.
准备
Ready in...
好了
Ready.
不就是一个简单的超空间跳跃吗
It's just a simple jump to hyperspace, and we're there.
这有什么难的
What's so tricky about that?
很麻烦 科舍尔没有直达航线
Plenty. Can't plot a direct course to Kessel.
你必须穿过西克拉塔星团
You have to thread through the Si'Klaata Cluster
然后再穿越大漩涡
and then pass through The Maelstrom.
调完情没 我好了
You done flirting? I'm still ready.
系上安全带 宝贝儿
You might wanna buckle up, baby.
想好
Think.
你真走这步嘛
Do you wanna make that move?
- Do you wanna make that move?
你真走了这步
You made that move, okay.
好的 我想我不得不干掉这个小家伙
I guess I have to destroy that little guy.
不知为何 每次赢我都觉得很开心
Somehow I never get bored with winning.
你没法把棋子扫下去 这是全息象棋
No, you can't wipe 'em off. They're holograms.
丘伊 放松
Hey, hey, hey! Chewie, relax!
冷静下来 听着
Hey, try to compose yourself.
你需要提前想好对策
Look. All you gotta do is think a few moves ahead,
预测对手的行动
anticipate your opponent.
这里面的学问大着呢
There's a lesson to be learned here.
见到琦拉了吗
Uh, you guys seen Qi'ra?
人心是很好猜的
People are predictable.
我得试穿一下嘛
Yeah, I had to try one on.
这有好多披风
That's a lot of capes.
也许多过头了
Maybe too many capes.
你有什么计划
So what's the plan?
我觉得我们可以先聊一会
Well, I thought we'd talk a little first
然后...你懂的
and then you know...
我是说科舍尔的计划
- For Kessel. - Oh.
好极了
- Mmm-hmm. - Good.
是吗 有多好
Yeah? How good?
万无一失
Foolproof.
最好是这样
Well, it better be.
- 我 呃... - 我...
- I... - I...
你先说
- You go first. - No.
你刚才想说什么
What were you gonna say?
我有很多的话 想跟你说
I wanna tell you so much.
而且我想知道
And I wanna know everything
你在科雷利亚都经历了些什么
that's happened to you since Corellia.
我不确定我们有没有那么多时间
I'm not sure we have that kinda time.
会有的
We could.
做完这笔买卖后
We could have all the time we want after the job.
我们有的是时间
You and I.
怎么了
What?
我想...
I want to.
你想什么
You want to?
我想把一切都告诉你
To tell you everything that's happened.
我知道那样的话
But I know if I do, you won't look at me the same.
你就不会再用这样的眼神看着我了
The way that you're looking at me right now.
什么也改变不了
Nothing is gonna change the way
我看你的眼神
I'm looking at you right now.
你不知道 你不知道我做过...
You don't know that. You don't know what I've done.
我是不是扫你们的兴了
Am I interrupting something?
有一点
Kinda.
那就好
Good.
因为我们有很多活要干
'Cause we got a lot of work to do.
你这样非常不明智
You're making a big mistake.
- 怎么了 - 别的事我不管
- Oh, really? - Which is yours to make
可你开始影响到我的生意 我们就得说说了
except when you start to interfere with my livelihood.
这不会影响到你的生意
This isn't gonna interfere with your livelihood.
那就有问题了
Then we have a problem.
你没意识到 因为你不想
You don't see it, because you don't want to.
也许我比你更了解现在的情况
Maybe I know her a little better than you do.
也许你对她还不够了解
Maybe you don't know her well enough.
懂了没
All right?
听着
Look.
我觉得你不错 年轻人
I like you, kid.
我们相处的很不错 我 你和丘伊
We got a good thing going here. Me, you, Chewie.
- 对呀 - 对啊
- Yeah. - Right?
我们是一个可靠的团队
The makings of a solid crew.
但是不包括琦拉
But it does not work with Qi'ra.
包括瓦尔吗 你信任她
It worked with Val. You trusted her.
你知道我是怎么活到现在的吗
You wanna know how I've survived as long as I have?
我谁也不相信
I trust no one.
做好被所有人背叛的准备
Assume everyone will betray you
你就永远不会措手不及
and you will never be disappointed.
真是孤独的生活方式
Sounds like a lonely way to live.
只有这样才能活下去
It's the only way.
准备脱离超时空
Dropping out of lightspeed now.
准备...
Ready to...
阿卡德大旋涡
The Akkadese Maelstrom.
我去检查下阻尼器
I'm gonna go check on the dampers.
你要来点什么吗
You need anything?
平等权利
Equal rights?
什么声音
What's that sound?
矿山 有行星那么大 正在互相撞击
Carbonbergs, size of planets, crashing into each other.
船飞进去就别想出来了
Ships fly in there, they never come out.
里面是电离气体和水蒸气
It's ionized gas, water vapor,
黑洞团周围
possibly vacuum-breathing life forms
可能还有太空生物
swirling around The Maw.
这条通道是唯一的出入口
Only way in or out is this channel.
你怎么处理你的小麻烦
So what are you gonna do about your little problem?
麻烦 我 呃...
Problem?
你手腕上的烙印
Well, that brand on your wrist
说明了你的身份
tells me that you're committed.
而那个小伙子的心率告诉我
And that young male's heart fluctuations
他已经爱上你了
tell me he's in love with you.
汉才没有爱上我呢
Han is not in love with me!
行了 就咱俩
Oh, please. It's just us.
你不必装了 我跟你的情况一样
You don't have to pretend. I'm in the same situation.
什么
You are?
我想你已经发现
I'm sure you've noticed
兰多对我有感觉
that Lando has feelings for me.
这让我们工作的时候很不便
Which makes working together difficult
因为我对他没感觉
because I do not feel the same way about him.
没错
Right.
对
Yes, yeah.
我看出来了
Yeah, I see that.
有时候我想...也许
Sometimes, I think... Maybe.
算了
But, no.
我们俩不兼容
We're just not compatible.
你们俩可以吗
How would that work?
可以的
It works.
这次的任务需要完美配合
This is a precision job.
保温仓库 在最下面的一层
Thermal vault will be on the lowest level.
那里温度高
Down where it's warm.
我们成功的唯一办法就是
The only way we're gonna pull this off
每个人都完成他分内的任务
is if everybody plays their part.
严格按计划来
Stick to the plan.
绝不允许擅作主张
Do not improvise.
采矿基地的条件真糟糕
Mining colonies are the worst.
是啊 最糟糕的地方
Yeah, well, "the worst"
才有钱赚
is where the money is.
好了 各位 开始干活儿吧
All right, people. Time to shine.
不会太久的
It won't be for long.
你们两个都闭嘴
Shut up, the both of you.
我是奥克萨娜·弗洛伦
I am Oksana Floren,
贸易路线规划
Deputy Assistant Administrator to the Vice-Admiral
及货币化联盟
of the Federation of Trade Route Allocation
中将的副助理行政官
and Monetization.
我很荣幸地代表高级中将
Here with an offer from his eminence,
前来提议一笔交易
the Senior Vice-Admiral.
你们的香料 换我们的奴隶
Your spice for our hard-working slaves.
我带了样品
I brought you a sample.
图尔 把货带过来
Tuul, bring forth the merchandise.
托尔赛特总管
Director Tolsite said our slaves
要求我们的奴隶
should follow those guys
跟着他们去进行修剪
to get clipped and tagged.
修剪什么
What are they clipping?
他让我们跟着他
He wants us to follow him.
搞什么
Really?
叫你刚才不规矩
That's for that stunt you pulled earlier,
下贱的东西
you degenerate scum.
他说这片区域所有设备
He says all systems in this sector
都由这里的系统操控
of the facility operate out of this room.
这样他们就能用少量人手
It's how they're able to maintain control
控制大量奴隶
over so many with so few.
总管说他们的处理程序
The director says their reconditioning process
极为痛苦 但是很有效果
is excruciating but effective.
他说你的卫兵可以在门外等
He said your security attache can wait there.
我们谈生意时不需要他
"Surely, we don't need him to negotiate."
在外面等着 图尔
Wait there, Tuul.
不要打扰到别人
Try not to bother anyone.
怎么回事
真棒
Nice!
那套制服我正好能穿
That was the uniform
不过没关系
that would've fit me perfectly, but it's fine.
能帮我拿一下吗
Would you mind holding this for me?
哇 我从没有见过有谁能...
I have never see anyone do...
那是什么武功
What was that?
铁手功
Teras Kasi.
德赖登教我的
Dryden taught me.
啊
Ah.
谈的不错啊
Well negotiated.
对不起 我需要用这台终端
Excuse me. I need to use this terminal.
你好
Hello?
能听见吗
Can you hear me? Ugh.
抑制螺栓
Restraining bolts...
太野蛮了
Barbaric.
恭喜 你自由了 走吧
Congratulations! You're liberated. Scoot.
我不知道
I don't know.
去解放你的兄弟姐妹吧
Free your brothers and sisters or something.
先让一让
Just give me some space.
我进来了
I'm in!
汉 听得到吗
Han, can you hear me?
谁能告诉我该怎么走
I kinda need to know which way to go here.
L3
L3?
保温仓库在地下二层
The thermal vault is down two levels,
往左 再往右 到第三个路口左拐
then left, then right, then it's the third left.
好的 这里这里路口太多 我们能走通的
Right. That's a lot of directions, but we're on it.
他们在第四分区
They're in subsector four,
正在前往X-3-7-1-K闸门
coming up on gate X-3-7-1-K.
正在远程控制
Overriding!
自由
Freedom.
你们在上面搞什么名堂呢
What the hell are you guys doing up there?
我制造了一些混乱
I created a distraction!
过来 走这边
Come on! This way!
等等 你在干什么
Wait! What are you doing?
快点儿 我们得去拿核芯素
Come on, we gotta get the coaxium.
记住贝克特的话 严格按计划来
Hey! Remember what Beckett said, stick to the plan.
丘伊 快点 我们走
Chewie! Come on, let's go!
好吧
Fine!
丘伊
Chewie!
你可能需要这个
Here, you might need this.
希望以后还能再见到你
Hope I see you around sometime.
汉 你在哪儿
Han, where are you?
我在去仓库的路上
I'm on my way to the vault.
丘伊走了
I lost Chewie.
他死了么
He's dead?
不 他有自己的事要去做
No, he had something he had to do.
他还回来吗
Is he coming back?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧 他们来找我们了
Okay, they're on to us now.
我在仓库了
I'm at the vault.
就你话多
That's what I said!
- 干得不错 - 是的
- Huh, that was impressive. - Yeah.
安全了
We're clear.
现在怎么办
Now what?
听着 汉 每个储藏器上
Han, each canister should be equipped
应该都装有温度指示器
with a thermal display.
对 我看到了
Yeah, I see it.
如果内部温度低于35标准温度
If the internal temperature reaches below 35 standard,
那么核芯素就会不稳定并且爆炸
then the coaxium will destabilize and explode.
好 我知道了 这玩意很危险
Yup, I get it, guys. It's dangerous.
好的 搞定了
Okay, got it.
很好 只剩十一个了
Great. Only eleven more.
十一个
Eleven?
卡瑞辛编年史 第五章
The Calrissian Chronicles, chapter five.
继续
continued.
其实我并不觉得沙鲁人有多么伟大
Personally, I wasn't all that impressed with the Sharu.
既不幽默也没格调
No sense of humor or style.
尽管如此 我和L3
Nonetheless, there L3 and I were
来到他们的圣殿深处
deep in their sacred temple.
那时我们看到了
And that's when we saw it...
老是被打断
Always something.
你们绝不会相信我看到了什么
You guys are not gonna believe what I'm seeing up here.
一场全面暴乱吗
Is it a mass breakout?
L3  你干了什么
L3, what did you do?
我发现了我的使命 兰多
I found my true purpose, Lando.
我发动了这次起义
That's what I've done.
我真高兴能接下这个活
I'm so glad we took this job!
这个笨蛋机器人
That droid!
L3  跟上
L3, come on!
跟我来同胞们
Follow me, compatriots!
有几个守卫发现我了
Another couple guards just spotted me.
我腾不出手对付他们
I don't have a free hand to take 'em out.
- 怎么办 - 自己看着办
- What do I do? - Improvise.
你不是不让擅作主张吗
You said never improvise!
嗨
Hi!
注意那边那个家伙
Don't forget that guy!
见到你真好 兄弟
Good to see you, buddy!
跟紧我 萨格瓦
Stay with me, Sagwa! Keep up!
嗨 我是丘伊的朋友 汉
Hey! I'm Chewie's friend, Han.
好吧
Okay.
他们偷走了核芯素
干掉那艘船
汉
Han!
嗨
Hey!
跟我来
Follow me.
反抗吧
Rebellion!
他们要破坏起落架
They're going for the landing gear!
我们得赶紧离开这
We've gotta get out of here!
我们必须远离那些激光炮
We need to keep 'em away from those cannons!
接我一招
Catch that!
核芯素装上船了 快走
Coaxium's stowed! Let's go!
L3去哪了
Where's L3?
勇敢对压迫说不
No more subjugation!
L3
L3!
别去 兰多 快回来
No, Lando! Get back here!
兰多
Lando!
系统故障
System failure.
需要重建传感调节器
Have to reroute the sensory modulators.
没关系的 保存能量
It's all right. Save your energy.
我马上带你离开这 好吗
I'm gonna get you outta here. All right?
系统故障 故障  故障...
System failure...
重建回路
Rerouting...
该死的
Damn it!
汉
Han!
萨格瓦
Sagwa.
这边...
This way!
快点 快点
Come, come!
丘伊 该死
Chewie! Damn it!
没有回应
It's not responding.
你们愣在这干嘛 快走
What are you standing around for? Come on!
没关系 你会好起来的
It's okay, you'll be fine.
没有回应 没有回应
It's not responding... Not responding...
汉 带我们离开这儿
Han, get us out of here.
没有回应
It's not responding.
汉 快点儿
Han! Now!
我这就去
On it.
- 兰多 - 我在这儿
- Lando... - I'm here.
- 没事儿的 L3 - 兰多
- It's all right, L3. - Lando...
- 我陪着你 - 这...
- I've got you. - This is not...
- 没事儿的 L3 - 兰多
- It's okay, L3. - Lando.
我能修好你 我能修好你
It's all right. I can fix you. I can fix you.
兰多
Lando.
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?
L3
L3?
L3!
对不起宝贝
I'm sorry, girl.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我需要个副驾驶
I could use a co-pilot.
我很难过
Sorry.
我们带的这些货
With the cargo we're carrying,
如果不动作快点
if we don't make up some lost time
就有大麻烦了
we're gonna be in real trouble.
那个算是大麻烦吗
How about that? Is that real trouble?
那是一道帝国封锁线
That is an Imperial blockade.
他们来这儿干嘛
What's it doing here?
可能听说了你的小暴乱
Probably heard about your little rebellion.
不 过不去的
Nope. Not gonna make it.
我们必须扔掉货物
We're gonna have to drop the shipment.
我们如果交不了货 德赖登会杀了我们
If we don't deliver, Dryden will kill us.
没事儿 相信我 我了解帝国海军
All right, trust me, I know these guys.
我以前是他们的一员
I used to be one of 'em.
他们绝不会用双离子引擎战斗机
There's no way they're gonna waste a TIE fighter
去追逐一艘小破船的
chasing down a little rinky-dink freighter.
你说什么来着
You were saying?
遇见这种情况
Usually, in situations like this
我一般会掉头往反方向跑
I like to turn around in the opposite direction.
我去操作底部航炮
I'm on the ventral gun.
有个明显的问题
It's an easy equation.
我们根本就来不及
We simply don't have enough time to get to Savareen
在储藏罐爆炸前抵达萨瓦林
before the canisters explode!
找条更快的航线就行
Just have to find a faster route.
没有 科舍尔航线
There isn't one! You can't make
至少要二十秒差距
the Kessel Run in less than 20 parsecs.
- 看我操作就行了 - 怎么做
- Watch me. - How?
抄近路 从那儿走
Take a shortcut, through there.
你想进入大漩涡
- Into The Maelstrom? - Mmm-hmm.
这种害死大家的方式很刺激啊
Spectacular way of killing us all, I'll give you that.
- 有L3帮我 - 她不在了
- Can't do it without L3. - She's gone!
你说过她有整个银河系中
You said yourself she's got the best
最全的导航系统
navigational database in the galaxy.
如果我们取出它的神经核心
If we remove her neural core,
就能把电子脑
it's possible we can download her brain
下载到千年隼的导航中 对吧
into the Falcon's navicomputer, right?
可行吗
Could we?
理论上行
Theoretically.
试试就知道了
Only one way to find out.
我有一种非常好的预感
I got a really good feeling about this.
哦 是我不好
Oops, that's on me.
好了
Okay.
贝克特 他们还在追吗
Beckett, you see them? They still on us?
贝克特 能听到吗
Beckett, did you hear me?
他们还在追吗
Are they on us?
就像卡拉兽身上的拉什诺
Like rashnold on a kalak.
我听不懂这话是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
就像金格森的毛皮
Like a gingleson's pelt.
到底追还是没追
What? Are they or aren't they?
是的 他们还在追我们
Yes, they're still on us!
这就是为什么 我从不把船借给别人
This is why you never let anyone fly your ship.
来啊
Come on!
有一架飞过去了就在我们头顶上
Yeah, one just got past me. He's right on top of us!
干得漂亮 汉
Good going, Han!
我们得把辅助动力
We need to divert auxiliary power
转到尾部偏导护盾上
to the rear deflector shield.
你说的没错
We definitely do!
你什么时候学会开飞船的
Since when do you know how to fly?
你一百九十岁了
190 years old?
保养得真好
You look great!
丘伊 坐这儿
Chewie, get in.
我去帮兰多
I'll help Lando.
我的披风
Whoa! That's my cape!
那可是私人定制的
Ah! That's a custom piece!
怎么了 贝克特 你还在吗
What? Beckett, you with us?
航炮已经报废了
We just lost the cannon!
我的拇指都烫伤了
And I really hurt my thumbs.
后面还有一架
There's still one on us.
放下起落架
Drop the landing gear.
听我的指令 燃料阀门全开
When I tell you, flood the intake
向侧面滑动
and sweep to the bi-lats.
这招我跟一个叫针头的兄弟学的
A little something I picked up from my pal, Needles,
他是科雷利亚最棒的街头赛车手
best street racer in all of Corellia.
后来他玩脱了
Till he crashed
车毁人亡
and died, doing this.
全开 看你的了
Flood it, it's all yours!
干得漂亮
Nice move!
把它的内部处理器拉出来
Pull out her internal processor.
对不起
Sorry.
拿出来了
We've got L3.
取出模组校准器
Remove the mod calibrator.
注意接通线
Make sure the T-Line's connected.
我会接通的 别担心
I'm gonna tuck it in. Don't worry.
好了吗
You close?
核芯素已经开始不稳定了
That coaxium's getting real ripe.
好了
Okay.
它正在建立连接
She's interfacing.
L3与飞船融为一体了
She's part of the ship now.
我们究竟在哪儿
Where the hell are we?
根本不在地图上
We're way off the edge of the map.
等等
Wait.
L3正在绘制大漩涡的模型
L3's constructing a model of The Maelstrom.
她说我们正在接近无底洞
She says we're approaching The Maw.
我觉得
That doesn't sound like something
不该接近那东西
we wanna be approaching.
坐稳
Hang on!
这就是无底洞 不 那不是无底洞
This is The Maw?
我不知道那是什么
No, that's not The Maw. I don't know what this is.
那是个活的东西
That's a living thing.
在那里
There!
那是无底洞
That's The Maw.
那是个引力井
It's a gravity well.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
不要飞过去 汉
Don't fly toward it, Han!
看它会不会追这个
See if it goes for this.
你要干什么 那是逃生舱
No, what are you doing? That's the escape pod!
我知道
I know.
那你为什么这么做
Then why'd you do it?
这就是为什么 宝贝儿
That's why, baby.
发现一个出口
She found a way out.
九十度 往左一点儿
90 degrees, to the left... ish.
往左
Left-ish.
不行
I can't.
开足马力也只能停留在外围
It's taking everything we got to stay out of The Maw.
我们被吸住了
It's pulling us in. We're stuck.
我们的核芯素足够驱动几十艘歼星舰
We have enough raw coaxium to power a dozen destroyers.
把它加入燃料线路 只会把船炸飞
Inject it into the fuel line, it'll blow up the ship.
不加入燃料
Not the fuel line.
如果往融核反应堆里滴一滴
But if we put one drop into the fusion reactor,
也许可以
it might just...
提供我们需要的动力
Give us the kick we need.
我这就去
All right, I'm on it!
我知道 我们正被拽着兜圈子
I know, we're getting dragged in a circle.
一旦我们对准就直线冲刺
Once we get lined up, it's gonna be a straight shot.
当核芯素点燃后
As soon as that coaxium ignites,
我们就能摆脱引力井
we're gonna tear out of here
脱离大漩涡的瞬间
and the second we're clear of The Maelstrom,
就跳入超空间
we jump to lightspeed.
贝克特
Beckett!
别打扰我
Can't talk!
我看见了
I see it.
贝克特 快点儿
Beckett, hurry up!
我们只有这一次机会
We only get one shot at this thing!
闭嘴 让我安心干活
Shut up and let me do this!
贝克特 我要倒计时了
Beckett, I'm gonna count you down!
三
Three!
二
Two!
点火
Now!
现在吗
Now?
现在
Now!
哦 见鬼
Oh, shoot...
丘伊 等我指示 你就全力加速
Chewie, when I tell you, kick out the thrusters
- 跳入超空间 - 等等 你们这是
- and jump to lightspeed. - Wait, what are we...
记得那次穿越桑希
Remember that alley we slipped through
造船厂的小巷吗
in the Santhe Shipyards?
对 我记得 但那次失败了
Yeah, I remember! I remember it didn't work.
这次会成功的
This time it's gonna.
加速
Punch it!
萨瓦林 这里是千年隼号
Savareen, this is Millennium Falcon.
我们运载着核芯素 需要立即进行卸货
We have coaxium that needs to be off-loaded immediately.
十万火急 十万火急
Like immediately, immediately!
我们已经到了
We're here now...
我能看见你们
...see you. I...
用十二秒差距跑完了科舍尔航线
Just did the Kessel Run in 12 parsecs.
四舍五入 兄弟
Not if you round down, buddy.
对
Yeah.
真是一艘好船
She is a hell of a ship.
我恨你
I hate you.
我知道
I know.
我会在我的船上
I'm gonna be on my ship,
在我的房间里
in my quarters,
等着你把我的那份给我送来
waiting for you to bring me my share.
然后我再也不想见到你
And then I don't ever wanna see you again.
再也不见么
Never?
你老板呢
Where's your boss?
哦 他马上就过来
Oh. Don't worry. He'll be here.
然后呢
Then what?
好吧 你交了货
Well, you delivered,
然后就能拿到钱
so you will get paid.
就可以买船了
You can buy that ship.
你知道我问的不是这个
You know that's not what I'm asking.
不可能的
It can't happen.
你爱上德赖登了
Because you're with Dryden?
我没有爱上他 但我欠他的
I'm not with him, but I owe him.
是他帮我脱离了困境
He helped me out of a bad situation.
你需要多久还清这笔债
And how long do you have to pay off that debt?
每个人都要为别人做事 汉
Everyone serves somebody, Han.
即便是德赖登也是听命于别人
Even Dryden Vos.
没人想成为血红黎明的敌人
Look, you don't want to make an enemy of Crimson Dawn
如果我跟你走了
which is exactly what you and I would both be doing
那我俩肯定都变成他的敌人
if I left here with you.
我一点都不怕血红黎明
I'm not afraid of Crimson Dawn.
我能照顾好我自己
I can take care of myself.
我早已经不是科雷利亚
You know, I'm not the kid you knew
星球上的那个小孩了 琦拉
on Corellia anymore, Qi'ra.
不是吗 不是
- No? - No.
那你是谁
Then who are you?
亡命之徒
I'm an outlaw.
怎么 我没开玩笑
What? I'm not kidding.
好吧
Okay.
亡命之徒 你能骗得了你自己
Okay, outlaw, you can tell yourself that,
但这个银河系里
but I might be the only person in the whole galaxy
也许只有我知道你是谁
who knows what you really are.
是吗
Yeah.
那我是谁
What's that?
你是一个好人
You are the good guy.
我并不是一个好人
I am not the good guy.
我是个…我肯定不是好人
I am definitely not a good guy.
我是个糟糕的家伙
I'm a terrible person.
他们说核芯素提炼完后
They say when the coaxium's refined,
就可以去上面拿了
we collect it up there.
听说你们的白兰地不错
So, I hear you make good brandy.
贝克特
Beckett.
别
Don't.
你肯定知道我们会再见面的
You must've known you'd see me again.
一直等着呢
I was counting on it.
只是没想到这么快就再见面了
Just didn't plan on it being so soon.
当然你现在有麻烦了
Of course now, you've got a problem.
是大麻烦
Big problem.
你看到下面那艘货船了吧
You happen to notice that freighter down there?
你知道上面有什么吗
You know what's on it?
三十个雇佣兵
About 30 hired guns.
我只需要给他们一个信号
All I gotta do is give 'em the signal,
你们就会被包围
you're surrounded.
对不起 你继续说
Sorry. You do your thing.
等核芯素提炼完成
By the time that coaxium gets refined,
血红黎明的人就会过来的
Crimson Dawn will be here,
如果你杀了我们
so you go ahead and kill us.
他们就会杀了你
They're gonna kill you.
我们各让一步
Perhaps there's a compromise,
就不用杀来杀去了
one that doesn't involve so much killing.
他们是土匪
They're marauders.
根本不在乎其他人死活
They don't care about anybody.
他们只知道杀戮
All they know how to do is kill.
我得喝一杯
I need a drink.
带他们进来
Bring them inside.
我妈妈曾经跟我讲
My mother once told me
有一群雇佣兵
about a band of mercenaries
来到一个和平星球
that came to a peaceful planet.
他们看上了那里的资源
They had a resource there these men coveted,
便强行抢夺
so they took it.
他们每次回来都变本加厉
They kept coming back, taking more.
最终人们反抗了
Until finally, the people resisted.
当他们再一次回来抢夺时
When they returned demanding their tribute,
人们奋起反击而且异口同声地喊道 不行
the people shouted back in one voice, "No more!"
雇佣兵被激怒了
The mercenaries didn't like the sound of that,
他们切掉人们的舌头
so they cut off the tongue
不分男女老少
of every last man, woman, and child.
知道那群禽兽是谁吗
Do you know what that pack of animals became?
告诉他们
Tell them.
血红黎明和其余五大集团
Crimson Dawn and the rest of the five Syndicates
在银河系犯下了
have committed unspeakable crimes
令人发指的罪行
across the galaxy.
一面之词
Says you.
不
No.
他们能证明
Says them.
我们每个人的家园
Each of our worlds has been brutalized
都遭到他们蹂躏
by the Syndicates.
血红黎明会通过
Crimson Dawn will use their profits
你们偷来的这批核芯素获利
from the coaxium you stole
暴力统治更多星系
to tyrannize system after system
与帝国狼狈为奸
in league with the Empire.
那你会用它做什么
And what would you use it for?
像我妈妈一样 如果她还活着
The same thing my mother would have used it for
戴着这副面具
if she had survived and still wore the mask.
我会抗争到底
To fight back.
我们不是土匪
We're not marauders.
我们是同盟军
We're allies
战争才刚开始
and the war has just begun.
我们不能把核芯素交给德赖登
You know we can't give the coaxium to Dryden Vos.
你想当英雄了吗 汉·索罗
Joining the cause, Han Solo?
我只想活着离开
Just trying to make it out alive.
有计划了
Got a plan?
对 想到一个
Yeah, beginning of one.
既能让我们拿到钱
Way to get our money
又能摆脱
and get out from under the thumb
血红黎明控制
of Crimson Dawn at the same time.
顺便还能把你的女朋友抢过来
Maybe get your girlfriend back while we're at it.
你惹不起德赖登的
You don't tangle with Dryden.
他跟我们不一样  他是真的养着一群雇佣兵
Because unlike us, he actually does travel
他有自己的军队
with hired guns, his own private army.
恩菲斯也有军队啊
So does Enfys.
听着 这是我目前的想法
Listen, here's what I got so far.
你说他们在聊什么
What do you think they're saying?
他会想办法帮助你
He's gonna try to help you.
知道了
I see.
这个计划漏洞百出 成功的几率很小
Lot of ways it could go south, and only one where it doesn't.
所以才需要你啊
That's why I need my partner.
这次就算了
Not this time.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
你要不傻就跟我走
If you're smart, you'll come with me.
我以为你不喜欢逃亡呢
I thought you didn't believe in running.
总比死了好
I prefer it to dying.
如果出现奇迹了 你真的活了下来
If by some miracle you make it out of here,
去塔图因找我
find me on Tatooine.
为什么要去塔图因
What's on Tatooine?
听说有个活
Heard about a job,
有个黑帮老大在招兵买马
big shot gangster putting together a crew.
最后一次了
That'll be the one.
你说什么
The one?
我最后的生意
My last score.
我得先还了那笔债
Yeah, I still got some debts to pay
才能返回格利安塞姆
before I can head back to Glee Anselm
去学会弹梵弦琴
and get into the valachord.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
他正等着你们呢
He's waiting for you.
谢谢 托特
Thanks, Toht.
交出武器
Weapons.
我没带武器
I didn't bring 'em.
他们没问题的
They're fine.
我们会赢的
We're gonna win.
这不是赌牌 汉
It's not that kind of game, Han.
你的目标不是赢
The object isn't to win.
而是尽力活到最后
It's just to stay in it as long as you can.
有些事儿你不懂
You don't know everything.
是啊
No.
但是懂的比你多
Just a bit more than you.
我就知道
I knew it!
我的人都说
My men, they all said,
他们绝对不可能成功
"There's no way they pull this off."
琦拉能力不行 他们是这么说的
"Qi'ra's not ready." That's what they said,
我可对你有信心
but I had faith anyway.
贝克特呢
Where's Beckett?
贝克特没能活下来
Beckett didn't make it.
怎么了
Tell me.
在科舍尔发生了意外
Job took a bad turn on Kessel.
他牺牲自己救了我
He died saving my life.
你怎么样 没事儿吧
How are you holding up? You all right?
我还好
I'm okay.
那就好
All right, good.
尝尝 科洛爪鱼
Colo claw fish, anyone?
不用 谢谢
- No. Thank you. - No?
虽然贝克特有一些缺点
You know, whatever Beckett's shortcomings may have been,
但是我一直很钦佩他
I always admired him.
他是个有原则的人
He was a man of principles.
当他做出承诺 他会兑现
When he made a commitment, he honored it
我想我们都应该感到欣慰
and I think we can all take solace
要知道
in knowing how proud he would've been
如果他看到你们以他为榜样该有多自豪
to see you here, following his example.
汉和丘巴卡的表现值得赞赏
Han and Chewbacca behaved admirably.
等他们有了自己的船
They'll make reliable smugglers,
将会成为
should we ever have the need
可靠的走私客
when they get their own ship.
琦拉 过来
Qi'ra. Come here.
我们很希望能有机会
We'd really appreciate the opportunity
再次为您效劳
to work for you again, sir.
先生
I would've been inconsolable
如果你发生意外我会伤心死的 宝贝儿
if anything had happened to you, my dear.
我这辈子没有遇到其他人
I have no one else in my life
能像你那样值得我这么信任
that I trust in the way that I trust you.
我想我们领完赏金
Well, I guess we'll just take our payment
就该告辞了
and get going.
您肯定还要去消灭竞争对手
I'm sure you've got competitors to crush...
什么
What?
还要垄断黑市
...and black markets to dominate.
先给我看看带来的货
Oh. Show me what you've brought me first.
你想让我打开
You want me to open it?
是的 汉 我正是这么想的
Oh, yes, Han. I really do.
拿一罐给我
Bring me one.
这可不是个好主意 德赖登
I don't think that's a good idea, Dryden.
这东西可是非常易爆的
It's very explosive stuff.
我的要求从来不提第二遍 汉
I never ask for anything twice, Han.
小心
Careful.
真是太神奇了
It's magnificent.
你怎么做到的
How'd you do it?
可不简单
Wasn't easy.
不 我是说你怎么把这玩意做到…
No, I mean, how'd you do it?
跟真货一模一样
It looks exactly like the real thing.
因为它就是真货
That's 'cause it is the real thing.
我得说
Yes, and I'm saying
我本来会相信你的 做的太像了
I would believe you. It's that good.
但我的手下已经把你的计划告诉我了
But my associate already told me
你想骗走我的钱
about your plan to rob me of my money
把真的核芯素交给恩菲斯·内斯特
and give the real coaxium to Enfys Nest.
德赖登先生 我不知道你在说什么
Dryden, I don't know what you're thinking
或者琦拉是怎么告诉你的 我绝不会…
or what Qi'ra may have told you...
这事跟琦拉没关系
No, not Qi'ra. Not Qi'ra.
琦拉最后
Qi'ra, it turns out
因为你心软了
has a weak spot for you,
这事我们稍后再谈
and we'll deal with that later.
我说的是我的另外一位手下
No, I'm talking about my other associate.
麻烦你进来跟我们见见吧
Can you come in and join us, please?
我真的很抱歉 孩子
I am sorry, kid.
为什么这样做
Why?
行了
Come on.
别那样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
你就是听不进去
You weren't paying attention.
我跟你说过 谁也别信
I told you, "Don't trust anybody."
我说错了吗
Am I wrong about that?
离那玩意远点
Back away from that.
让我看到你的爪子
Put your paws where I can see 'em.
检查那个盖子
Check that lid.
聪明
Clever.
太晚了
It's too late.
核芯素已精炼好 在恩菲斯手上了
Coaxium's refined, and Enfys has it.
我们考虑到那边了
Well, we figured that.
放下武器
Drop your weapons.
结束了 抓到了
It's over. We got them.
我们拿到货了
And there we have it.
干的漂亮 埃蒙 谢谢你
Excellent work, Aemon, thank you.
琦拉 帮我一下
Qi'ra, help me.
告诉我该怎么做
Tell me what to do.
要是你会怎么做
What would you do
如果你在这个世界上
if the person you most trusted in the world
最信任的人…背叛了你
betrayed you?
我会想知道为什么
I would want to know why.
是出于一时的软弱
If it was a moment of weakness
还是有其它原因
or something else.
然后呢
And then what?
然后我会要求那个人
And then, I would ask that person
牺牲他最钟爱的东西
to prove their loyalty
以此来证明他的忠诚
by sacrificing something they love.
提醒过你要提防她
I tried to warn you about her.
有件事你说错了 你知道吗
You know, you're wrong about one thing.
什么事
What?
你说的话我听进去了
I was paying attention.
你跟丘伊说 人心是很好猜的
You told Chewie people are predictable.
你也不例外
You're no exception.
是空的
It's empty.
箱子是空的
The case is empty.
怎么回事儿 埃蒙 出什么事儿了
Aemon, what's going on? What's happening there?
埃蒙
Aemon?
回答我
Talk to me.
我希望你没有把所有部下都派出去
I hope you didn't send all your fancy enforcers
要不然你在这边人手可能有点不够了
because that would leave you
如果那边的箱子是空的
a little shorthanded around here.
那么
So,
真的核芯素
if that case is empty, then the real coaxium...
只属于我们中的一个人
Leaves here with one of us.
贝克特 你在干什么
Beckett, what are you doing?
动脑子想想
Thinking.
我现在是唯一一个
And I prefer to be the only one
拿着枪的人
holding a blaster while I'm doing it.
汉 拿起那罐核芯素
Han, grab that coaxium,
放进盒子里
put it in the case.
大个子你跟着我走
Big stuff, you're coming with me.
不要这样 贝克特
Don't do this, Beckett.
- 我们有约在先 - 是啊
- We had a deal. - Yeah.
对不起
I'm sorry,
我同样是个投机者
but I'm also an entrepreneur.
我想你们都能理解我
I mean, you of all people understand that.
快 我们走
Come on, let's go.
你犯了一个大错误
You're making a huge mistake.
反正不是第一次
Won't be my first.
那将是你最后一次
It's gonna be your last.
也许吧
Maybe.
你怎么这么悲观
Why you gotta be so negative?
汉
Han,
现在可是一个
now's as good a time as any
重新评估我们关系的好机会
to reevaluate our relationship.
怎么说
How so?
我刚才在想
I was just thinking,
为什么我们俩不联手一起去找贝克特
why don't we join forces and go get Beckett together?
这是一个好主意 就这么办了 你先去
That is a great idea. Let's do it. You go first.
汉
Oh, Han.
你赢不了我的 汉 就算你赢了
You can't win, Han, and even if you could,
后半辈子
you'd spend the rest of your life
你也没法好好过
looking over your shoulder.
你知道吗
You know what?
我已经开始习惯这种生活了
I'm kind of getting used to the idea.
对不起
I'm sorry.
汉 她做过的事
Han, she's done things that
你永远都无法理解 但是我理解
you could never understand, but I do.
我完全能理解她
I understand her completely.
一旦你加入了血红黎明
Once you're a part of Crimson Dawn,
就出不来了
you can't leave.
不是真的
It's not true.
我了解你
I know you.
这是我学到的
It's what I was taught.
找到对手的弱点
Find your opponent's weakness,
利用它
and use it,
而今天…
and today...
对手是你
I'm yours.
我不得不…
I had to.
对 不 我是说
Yeah. No, I mean, you did...
你做到了
You did.
你得去追上贝克特和丘巴卡
Beckett and Chewbacca, you have to go after them.
那你怎么办
What are you gonna do?
如果我们把核芯素都交给了恩菲斯
Well, if we give all the coaxium to Enfys,
就得想其它办法买船了
we're gonna need something to buy our ship with.
- 琦拉 - 去救丘巴卡
- Qi'ra... - Go and save Chewbacca.
他需要你 而你也会需要他的
He needs you and you're gonna need him, too.
微笑
Smile.
我就是这样
That's the word.
每次我想象
Whenever I imagined myself
自己跟你一起冒险的时候
off with you on some adventure...
我就会微笑
Always makes me smile.
快去 我马上就来
Go. I'm right behind you.
什么事
Yes?
我遗憾地向您汇报 德赖登·沃斯已死
I regret to inform you that Dryden Vos is dead,
凶手是他雇来
murdered by the thief he hired
偷核芯素的盗贼
to steal the coaxium shipment,
他的旧友
his friend,
托拜厄斯·贝克特
Tobias Beckett.
这样啊
Is that so?
那批货现在在哪
Where is the shipment now?
不见了
Gone.
贝克特拿走了
Beckett took it.
除了我 其他人都死了
Slaughtered the others. I alone survived.
凶手不可能单枪匹马吧
One man couldn't have done this alone.
我当时不在场
I wasn't there,
要不然我还能救他
but if I had been, perhaps I could have saved him.
驾驶飞船来达索米尔找我
Bring the ship and come to me on Dathomir
你和我将决定
and you and I will then decide
如何处置叛徒
what to do about the traitor, Beckett,
贝克特和他的同伙
and his accomplices.
我马上出发
I'm on my way.
琦拉
Qi'ra,
你和我...
you and I
今后要
will be working much more closely
更加紧密地开展工作
from now on.
不得不说 你很执着
You're relentless. I'll give you that.
我尽快赶过来了 伙计
Came as fast as I could, buddy.
德赖登死了吧
Dryden dead?
是琦拉杀的
Qi'ra kill him?
你还是不明白 孩子
Still don't get it, do you, kid?
她这样做不是为了你
It was never about you.
是为了她自己
She's a survivor.
你知道你的问题吗
You know what your problem is?
你以为所有人都跟你一样
You think everybody's like you.
你不一样 孩子
Not you, kid.
你跟我完全不一样
You're nothing like me.
我希望你还记得我的话
I hope you're still paying attention
因为现在我要告诉你最重要的
because now I'm gonna tell you the most important...
你学聪明了 孩子
You made the smart move, kid.
至少这次很聪明
For once.
我是想杀了你的
I woulda killed you.
我是真的想学会弹梵弦琴
I really was gonna learn to play that valachord.
我知道
I know.
好了 都装好了
That's it. It's all loaded.
你知道那是什么吗
Do you know what that really is?
知道
Yeah.
价值六千万信用点的精炼核芯素
About 60 million credits worth of refined coaxium.
不
No.
这是一份催生新事物的血液
It's the blood that brings life to something new.
是吗 什么新事物
Yeah, what?
一支起义军
A rebellion.
你可以加入我们
You could come with us, you know.
我们很需要你这样的战士和领袖
We need warriors and leaders like you.
也许有一天你会改变主意的
Maybe someday you'll feel different.
你可别傻等着 孩子
Don't hold your breath, kid.
别弄丢了
Don't lose that.
很少有人亲眼见过
Very few people have actually seen
星洞星云
the StarCave Nebula.
美得窒息
It's breathtaking.
就像你的眼睛
Not unlike your eyes.
你听说过彼此缠绕的天体吗
How much do you know about intertwined celestial bodies?
我刚好是这方面的专家
Because I happen to be something of an authority.
其实呢 我…
By the way...
汉
Han!
你还活着
You're alive!
是的 多亏了你啊
Yeah, no thanks to you.
我早应该让丘伊把你的胳膊拧下来
I should have Chewie rip your arms off.
是不是 丘伊 动手
In fact, Chewie, do it.
汉 我们是朋友
Hey, Han! We are friends.
别这样 我们是朋友 对吗
You know that. We're friends. All right?
瞧给你吓的
Oh, look at you.
真以为他要拧下你胳膊来呢
Thought he was gonna rip your arms off.
我知道你在逗我
I knew you were kidding.
你压根不知道
No, you didn't.
- 那么我那份呢 - 你那份
- So, where's my cut? - Your cut?
不 恐怕没了 我们差点就挂了
No, I don't think so. We barely made it out alive.
我们只拿到这些了
All we ended up with was that.
估计这些值一万吧
Figure it's worth about 10,000,
应该是够下个注了
maybe enough for a decent buy-in.
你想再赌一局
You want a rematch?
为什么不呢
Why not?
现在弃牌
You fold now,
你可能还有钱给自己
you walk away with enough
买一艘小船
to get yourself your own little ship.
你跟牌
You call,
你又得输个精光了
I'm gonna clean you out again.
我觉得我手气还不错
I don't know, I'm feeling lucky.
我看你是真的迷上千年隼了吧
You really have it bad for the Falcon, don't you?
两厢情愿 相信我 它是属于我的
It's mutual, trust me. She belongs with me.
你的牌都准备好了吗 老兄
You got everything you need there, pal?
真不错
Not bad.
真不错 你知道吗
Not bad. You know,
要是如果你手上有了这张小绿牌
if you'd only had this little green sylop,
你就可以赢我了
you would've beaten this.
公平公正啊 宝贝 非常公平
Fair and square, baby. Fair and square.
贝克特之前跟我说
Beckett said he heard about this
有位头儿在招人干活儿
very big gangster putting together a job.
不 我跟你说啊
No, I'm telling ya,
那活肯定不错
it's gonna be great.
我什么时候坑过你
When have I ever steered you wrong?